Welcome to Manulife Vitality Stories!
Once upon a time, Vivian wondered, “What is Manulife Vitality, anyway?”
So she jumped right into Chapter 1.
So many Canadians – including Vivian – felt like life insurance was just one of those things you kinda have to have.
Where’s the fun in that?
So why not make it fun?
Why not transform it into a way for Canadians to save on their insurance, earn discounts on popular brands and live better, healthier lives?
That’s why Manulife brought Vitality to life insurance.
You caught that bit about saving on insurance, right?
Vivian sure did – and she learned about it in Chapter 2!
it’s totally true:
if you have Family Term with Vitality Plus or Manulife UL with Vitality Plus,
you can save on the cost of your insurance.
You’ll save 10% in your first year, and you can earn even more savings in later years.
But, Vivian wondered, how?
To answer that, let’s move on to Chapter 3.
Members like Vivian can earn Vitality Points through workouts, steps, sleep quality, vaccinations, dental checkups, completing health reviews – there are just so many ways!
Those physical activities can be recorded with most wearable devices, like Apple Watch, Garmin, Fitbit and WHOOP, so you can easily get points.
And as your points increase, so does your Vitality Status and your insurance savings.
Vivian also clocked that bit about savings on popular brands.
In Chapter 4, she got a taste of what she (and you!) can get…
Check them out!
Here’s a hot tip! You can work your monthly payments for Apple Watch down to $0 per month by earning points through workouts and steps.
As we close with Chapter 5, Vivian knew with all those savings and rewards –
not to mention the health benefits – she’d live happily ever after.
Want to check out more Manulife Vitality “how-to” stories?
Click on one of the other videos you see here, then you could live happily ever after!